mycci.net 2015-12-21

# Consolidated.net - Privacy Policy

## Information Collection and Use

Consolidated Communications is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Consolidated Communications collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

## Registration

In order to add information to this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact and some personal information (such as name, email address, gender, birthdate and zip code). The information you provide here will only be used to maintain your account, help customize advertising and content to your demographic profile and to investigate any suspected abuse of our Terms of Service. It is optional for the user to provide extensive personal information (such as interests, hobbies, etc.) but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user�s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates, unless the user has enabled the 'Remember this Password' option upon Sign On. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited to simply browse and not add to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Consolidated Communications are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to an alert from LockOn, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

## Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users� information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as a password), that information is encrypted and is protected with a proprietary encryption solution.

All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind locked doors.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [info@lockon.com](mailto:info@lockon.com).

## Supplementation of Information

In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 

## Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the account creation page or by emailing our User Support. 

## Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our registration and Add forms all have an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who submit info to these services, but don't want any LockOn promotional material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive any of our newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by deselecting said alerts in the 'Edit Subscriptions' area of the LockOn Control Panel.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
